[theme music playing]
We Ardientes are the
rightful leaders of this town.
That is why we're going
to have Diego killed.
[Raul] Have our men guard Diego in jail.
I'm sure the Ardientes aren't happy
about the results of the survey.
If things get out of hand,
you know what to do.
Break Diego out.
Why don't you accompany me?
[Ivy] I have a bad feeling about this.
Let's go home.
[evil laugh]
-Natalie?!
-In the flesh.
-What's your problem, Natalie?
-You murdered my poor father!
It's payback time, Emilia!
Bad news, Congressman.
Jaguar's men broke into
the station and rescued Diego
from the hands of our men.
-We're Jaguar's men. Let's go!
-I don't care!
I'm not going with you!
You really are stubborn. Jaguar was right.
Wait! Who's Jaguar?!
[Rufo] Jaguar says you're
the one who needs him.
He will help you with your candidacy.
I'll defeat the Ardientes
using the force of the masses.
What I want is change for Ardiente,
not to replace one demon
with another demon.
[Ivy] I need to get out of here.
-Hello, Raul?
-Emilia?
Save me because Natalie
is going to kill me.
Save me now!
-[Natalie screaming]
-[gunshot]
That bastard Jaguar is really
making my blood boil!
He's obviously challenging me!
[Arnaldo] Why? What happened?
[Julio] He kidnapped your mother and Ivy.
We need to save them.
[Julio] Jaguar is really getting
on my nerves.
[screaming] [slapping]
Emilia! Emilia!
[crying]
Worst day of my life, Ivy!
This is the worst day of my life!
That Natalie…
This isn't over.
I will get back at that woman!
-Shh!
-The way she humiliated me…
[sobbing]
That's enough.
That's enough, Emilia.
You're Emilia Ardiente.
Crying doesn't suit you.
Emilia, if you're going
to have someone killed,
you should include their whole family.
And you should make sure they're all dead
so they won't take revenge on you.
Well, I understand Natalie
because if I were in her position,
flies would be swarming
all over you by now.
[ominous music playing]
Are you really my friend?
Whose side are you on?
You know, sometimes, I wonder if
you're really on my side, Ivy.
Because look at what you're doing.
And I'm also wondering
about… about that Jaguar.
Why did he save me?
[ominous music continues]
Well, whatever his reason may
be, the important thing is…
Emilia Ardiente is still alive.
So, you have a chance to find
out who Jaguar really is.
-[sobbing]
-[ominous music playing]
Raul?!
Natalie.
-What?
-What's your problem?
Why did you deny me of my prey?!
Natalie, it's not the right moment.
It isn't Emilia's time yet.
It isn't Emilia's time?
Or you can't live without her?
Let's admit it, Raul.
The truth is, you can't live
without your wife.
You feel so invincible.
You feel like an alpha male
because she boosts your ego.
She's so crazy about you.
No matter what you do to her,
no matter how many times
you cheat on her,
she's still there for you.
Wait, why are you saying this?
Admit it!
Are you jealous?
I'm irritated.
Irritated?
[tense music playing]
Natalie, listen.
All I need is for you to trust me.
Trust that you'll get what you want.
I trust you,
but don't you dare break that.
Now, if you trust me,
you need to lie low for a while.
Natalie, you're in danger.
Especially now that Emilia knows
who she's up against.
She won't stop
until she knows you're dead.
Just wait a little more.
Wait until I've stripped
the Ardientes of their power,
then you can strike again.
I need to go.
Emilia's waiting for me.
[tense music continues]
Okay.
But you better think of a good excuse.
I might've said you were good in bed.
Emilia, stop crying.
It doesn't suit you.
You'll really allow someone
like Natalie to get to you?
[crying]
Come here.
[slapping]
I don't deserve this.
I don't deserve this!
Do I deserve this? I don't, right?
Yes, you don't. You don't deserve this.
Of course not.
[crying]
Stop crying.
It doesn't suit you, trust me.
And why won't this damn car start?!
Damn it!
[sobbing]
-[action music playing]
-[laughing]
-[crying]
Sorry.
Sorry, Emilia. I'm sorry.
Sorry, I'll stop.
-You're mocking me again.
-No.
-You are!
-No…
Emilia.
-[honking]
-It's Arnaldo!
[Ivy] Hon!
Hon!
[Emilia crying]
-Hon!
-Emilia!
Hon!
-[Ivy] Hon!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm okay. I'm fine.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
[somber music playing]
How are you? Are you hurt?
[Arnaldo] How did you escape?
Ivy helped me escape.
That crazy ex of yours, Arnaldo…
How are you?
Are you worried about me or Natalie?
[ominous music playing]
What?
Wait.
Why are you bringing Natalie up, Emilia?
Raul, she's your mistress!
You have a new mistress!
Emilia, listen. Stop saying that.
What does Natalie have to do with this?
I… Emilia, Natalie isn't
the kind of woman… Come on!
First of all Emilia,
she's your son's ex-girlfriend.
Why would I pursue her?
Why would I go for someone like her?
You know what?
That's why your father hates me!
It's because of all your accusations!
And they're all false!
Emilia, I will never leave you for her.
If you only knew how worried
I was about you.
You can ask Arnaldo if you want, Emilia.
[crying]
Can you please stop being paranoid?!
[dramatic music playing]
Raul.
I'm here. Calm down.
And Ton says Jaguar has a huge net worth.
If he's really working with Natalie.
That means Pablo had a lot of connections.
But it doesn't make sense.
If Jaguar really was our enemy,
why'd he let Emilia go?
[tense music playing]
To send a message
that we are at his mercy.
Damn. This Jaguar is really
getting on my nerves.
There's no point being upset with Jaguar.
Nothing bad happened to Ivy.
And he even let Emilia go.
Shouldn't you be grateful, instead?
[scoffs]
Grateful?!
I'd rather kill myself
than thank that bastard, Jaguar.
I should have killed him
when I got the chance.
I should have followed him
and shot him in the head,
so my problems would be over.
But now, I am going to
make him my project.
Because I will kill that man.
[tense music continues playing]
I won't allow Diego's accomplice
or some hotsie-patootsie
woman like Natalie
to ruin the name Ardiente.
Hon, just sleep here for tonight.
Come on. Natalie might come back for you.
I'll kill her if she tries.
Honey, relax. I'm okay now.
And I'll have my bodyguards
with me, so I'll be okay.
Well, when it comes to your protection,
I don't trust anyone else but me.
So, please stay.
Come on.
I can't relax knowing
you could be in danger.
Hon…
Please?
Okay.
Thank you.
Honey…
Your grandfather mentioned
Diego has a new ally.
[slow tense music playing]
Is he working with the Jaguar?
[sighs] Well, yes.
We planned to have Diego killed,
but he managed to survive,
thanks to Jaguar's help.
And now he has constant
protection because of that.
Diego's really lucky, then.
He even found a new ally.
He's lucky to be alive, right?
Yeah…
which puts me
in a very difficult position.
If they continue to work together,
I will lose the election.
I can't allow Diego to beat me.
Honey…
I don't see that happening.
Huh?
I don't think Diego can beat you.
Of course.
He will never beat me,
knowing that I have you.
My secret weapon.
Of course.
[slow tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ivy] The same weapon
that'll cut you down.
[mobile phone ringing]
-Lily, finally!
-Mom.
I'm so glad you called.
How are you?
I'm fine.
But Diego…
The Ardientes tried to get rid of him.
Arnaldo tried to have him killed.
What?
[exhales sharply]
But he's okay, Mom. Someone helped him.
Who did?
It was the Jaguar.
A leader of a syndicate
going against the Ardientes.
Lily, have a bad feeling
about this Jaguar.
Me too.
Even if he's going against the Ardientes,
Diego shouldn't trust him.
He really needs to be freed
from prison soon.
Okay, Lily. I'll take care of that.
I need to set my plans in motion, Mom.
Because the longer we wait,
the more complicated things get.
Just take care, okay?
I will, Mom. Mom, you take care too.
Let's just keep each other updated.
Okay, then.
Be careful, okay?
[tense music playing]
Ivy.
I won't stay long.
This is from Diego.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
[Diego] Your plans need to push through.
Don't sacrifice seeking justice for me.
I can take care of myself.
I love you so much.
[romantic guitar music playing]
Don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
Diego, your life is at stake.
What the Ardientes did to you
was against human rights!
[Georgina] Camia's right.
But don't worry.
The judge was already inhibited
from handling your case.
We're just waiting
to see who will replace her.
Then we'll file for an appeal.
Diego…
We already have enough evidence
to prove your innocence.
So, don't worry.
You'll get out of here soon.
[slow tense music playing]
[mobile phone ringing]
Hello?
Yes.
Judge Otico.
Very well.
Then set a court appearance
as soon as possible.
Thank you.
So we have a new judge.
Let's just hope she isn't
a lapdog of the Ardientes.
Diego's lawyer already called me.
They asked me to set a court appearance.
Very good. Just stick
to the plan, Judge Otico.
Understood, Jaguar.
All right, just wait for your bonus.
You're really generous, Jaguar.
But remember, I'm a vicious enemy too.
[tense music playing]
Once I'm done helping Diego.
I'll deal with you, Emilia.
Jaguar.
Have you sent the gifts?
Yes.
I'm sure she received it by now.
[suspenseful music playing]
Emilia, don't open it.
-Who knows? It's a bomb.
-[tense music playing]
Auntie, Jaguar told me to open it.
So, I should open it.
What if…
Natalie sent that?
Auntie, Jaguar saved my life.
So why would he kill me right away?
I'll open it.
[tense music continues]
Wow.
A cellphone.
I'll read it.
CALL ME, MY BEAUTIFUL.
[scoffs]
"Call me, my beautiful".
Jaguar's quite the sweet-talker, no?
Just like Raul?
Auntie, all men are like that.
I'll call him.
[tense music continues]
[mobile phone ringing]
Are you sure she won't recognize my voice?
She won't, Jaguar.
[mobile phone ringing]
Hello, Jaguar?
Hello, beautiful.
Did I make your day?
Can you just stop the flowery words?
What exactly do you want from me?
It's simple.
I want you.
Well, if you really want me,
then show yourself.
You can't hide under your mask forever.
Then let's meet.
But I have one condition.
Condition? Okay. Tell me.
I want it to be just the two of us.
No one else.
[tense music intensifies]
[tense music continues playing]
I'm ready for you, Jaguar.
I hope you are too.
[ominous piano music playing]
This is it.
Emilia.
Yes, Aunt Claire?
There's a limousine
waiting for you outside.
It's from Jaguar.
That man is full of surprises, Auntie.
Take care, Emilia.
A man who is as clever and sly as him…
can be the most dangerous predator.
Remember that.
Don't worry, Auntie.
Remember this too.
A woman in red is fierce and smart enough
to make a sly man fall for her.
[ominous music playing]
I shall go now, Auntie.
[tense music playing]
Why?
Cut it out, Honey.
You've been like this all day.
-Well, I just…
-Wow, so clingy!
Your hands are all over the place.
I feel more comfortable
when you're close by.
You know, I'm just…I'm
just worried, that's all.
Worried? About what?
Well…
Honey, whatever you're worried about…
If it's about me, then don't be.
You should worry more about Diego.
Hon, do you think…
our wedding's getting in the way?
Maybe we should focus
on your campaign more.
Remember, when it came
to the survey results…
[slow tense music playing]
Diego had the upper hand.
No.
You're not getting in the way,
and neither is our wedding, okay?
Don't ever think that.
The wedding will go as planned.
I don't care about those survey results.
The election's a long way off.
I can catch up.
What's important now is our marriage.
I can lose everything else, but not you.
You're mine, Ivy.
You're mine. And, I'm yours.
Okay?
I guess our engagement party's
in full swing, then?
Yes.
But with some minor adjustments.
Like what exactly?
Nothing much.
I just want to make
our engagement party public.
You know people like love stories.
So, my plan is to hold
our engagement party
on the same day
as our campaign kick-off party.
Let's see if my ratings
don't go up after that.
Nice idea, Hon. You have my full support.
Thank you very much.
[suspenseful music playing]
[line ringing]
Hello?
Jaguar, I'm finally
in your lair. Where are you?
Looks like someone's a little too excited.
I can tell because you're in red tonight.
So, where are you already?
I'm running out of patience, you know.
All right, if that's what you want.
But before I reveal myself,
go through that door first.
I have a surprise waiting for you.
Wow, Jaguar.
What if I fall for you
and you aren't ready?
[slow tense music playing]
There's your favorite wine.
Help yourself.
So… Where are you?
How about you turn around, Emilia?
[suspenseful music playing]
You truly are a sly being, Jaguar.
I'm just being true to myself.
I'm just fast, agile, strong,
and, most of all, sly.
Well, if you really are fast,
strong, and sly, then,
why don't you come closer?
You Ardientes are so impatient.
We just met each other, Emilia.
You'll know my true nature soon enough.
But, first…
I need to look into
the depths of your soul.
My soul?
Emilia…
you should know
how obsessed I am with you.
That's why I saved you
from Natalie, remember?
Obsessed?
I want to steal you away
from your husband.
I want to set you free.
And I want my love
to be the one to help you.
I'm already free, Jaguar.
[scoffs]
Let's not fool ourselves.
You aren't free.
Until now, you're still being controlled.
By your father, your son,
and even by his fiancée.
And, most especially,
by your beloved.
But now, it's different.
I'm here to change the rules of the game.
I'll make you stronger.
I'll make all your dreams come true.
And, I'll show you how it feels
to be worshipped, to be feared.
I'll only believe you
if you come closer and show me your face.
[suspenseful music playing]
Very well.
Turn around then.
Okay.
I promise you that,
once you open your eyes,
you'll finally know…
the real Jaguar.
Go on, close your eyes.
[slow tense music playing]
[tense piano music playing]
I'LL MAKE YOUR DREAMS COME TRUE.
BUT FIRST, HELP ME TAKE DOWN JULIO.
[pensive music playing]
Did that just really happen?
[exhales sharply]
I can't believe this.
Am I becoming an adulteress?
Or am I becoming like Raul?
I'LL MAKE YOUR DREAMS COME TRUE.
BUT FIRST, HELP ME TAKE DOWN JULIO.
[ominous music playing]
The facts of the case show
the evidences against
my client are circumstantial.
He may have a witness,
but there's nothing that
could corroborate his statement,
so it's his word against my client's.
And I'm telling you, the witness
is perjuring himself.
With all due respect,
we all know why Diego is in prison.
That's because the judge
who used to handle this case
works for the Ardientes.
I can understand your
frustration, Atty. Fisher.
And Miss Cruz,
I've already reviewed the case
and found out that you're right.
Mr. Torillo is in prison
for a crime he didn't commit.
Does that mean that Diego can go free?
It depends.
If he agrees to my condition.
What is it?
He should allow the Jaguar
to be his backer and supporter
during the election.
[tense music playing]
I'd rather rot in prison
than become Jaguar's lapdog.
There's no law that states
I can't run for election
while I'm in jail,
so we'll keep fighting.
Even though I'm in prison,
I will still become a governor.
[Camia sighing]
Diego, don't worry.
I'll take charge of the campaign.
[somber music playing]
You're right that we can't
trust Jaguar so easily.
We don't know him
or just what he's capable of.
But Lily, what about Diego?
Mom, I'll find a way to help free Diego.
But for now, I need to find out
who Jaguar is first.
That way, before we meet with Judge Otico,
we'll know what to do.
Diego will get out of prison
through legal means.
[somber music continues playing]
Jaguar…
Hmm…
[singing]
[humming]
It looks like you're having
a good day, Emilia.
I heard you met with Jaguar.
What does he look like? Is he handsome?
[tense music playing]
Honestly, I wouldn't know.
He seems to be a mysterious man.
What did he say?
What did you talk about?
Did he offer help?
Not really.
But I remember him saying that
he wants to steal me from you.
He said that?
Mhm.
[scoffs]
That bastard is out of his mind.
He's insane.
He said that?
Are you jealous?
Me? Jealous? Why would I be jealous?
Huh? Why?
Will you leave me for him?
I'm talking to you.
Are you going to leave me?
You won't, right?
Besides, he's our family's enemy.
If your father finds out
you're making deals with him,
you'll be in big trouble.
Wait. How'd you find out about the deal?
This.
You left this lying around.
If your father finds out about
this, you know what will happen.
[tense music continues playing]
Be careful next time.
Okay. I'll keep it.
Emilia, Raul.
Julio wants to see us.
What they're doing to Diego is too much!
That's right!
Let's fight for Diego!
Let's organize a rally
in front of the office
of those corrupt judges!
[all] That's right! Let's hold a rally!
Hold on! Wait!
Please calm down!
Calm down!
Diego said we shouldn't worry about him.
We should just focus on our campaign.
Let's generate buzz for Diego.
And let's show those Ardientes
that even though Diego's in prison
and that they have control
over this entire province,
we can beat them if we work together.
-That's right, Ms. Camia.
-Friends.
Let's do this for Diego!
[all] For Diego!
For real change!
[all] For real change!
[applauding]
-Diego!
[tense music playing]
You will all make
a public appearance tomorrow.
That way, we could invite the public
to the kick-off party
of Arnaldo's campaign.
Yes, Grandpa.
We will also invite them
to our engagement party.
The more they feel included,
the more inclined
they'll be to support us.
[slow tense music playing]
[Julio] That's right.
Now.
Reminder.
Please.
I don't want another scandal tomorrow.
Keep it friendly.
I want everyone to smile
and be on their best behavior.
Especially you, Emilia.
Control your emotions.
[mouthing]
How are you guys doing?
You're running out of bags.
Replenish them, okay? Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Loring] Let's get more over there.
[Pandoy] But these are already divided.
It's great that it's here in town…
[tense music playing]
THE ARDIENTES WILL MAKE
A PUBLIC APPEARANCE TO INVITE
[phone chimes]
THE ARDIENTES WILL MAKE
A PUBLIC APPEARANCE TO INVITE
THE PUBLIC TO ARNALDO'S
CAMPAIGN KICK-OFF PARTY.
GENERATE BUZZ FOR DIEGO TOO.
WE'RE READY FOR THE ARDIENTES.
[phone buzzing]
Hello, everyone.
Please have this.
I prepared something for you
so don't miss it, okay?
-See you there!
-Tell the others too.
Bring your friends, your families.
Everyone you want.
-Oh, our enemies.
-Diego might be in jail,
but he still won in the second survey.
That means we are all sick
of the Ardientes.
Good grief, Camia.
What are you doing here?
The right thing, Emilia.
You don't own Ardiente, so we
can campaign anywhere we want.
[sighing]
Let's go.
Let's go and find another place.
Come on, everyone.
Good idea. You are so right, son.
We should leave
and look for a place
without trash lying around.
Emilia, you're the one who's garbage!
You are all trash!
You framed Diego,
you good-for-nothing cheaters!
-[slapping]
-Shut up!
-You should shut up!
Ms. Camia…
Wait! You can't stop me.
Hold this.
-[tense music playing]
-[Marlon] Wait.
[Ivy] Emilia!
Emilia, that's enough!
Camia!
-Stop them!
-That's enough!
I told you to stop them!
That's enough!
Camia!
You ruined my hair!
Is that all you got, Emilia?
Or do you want me to shove
your face into the mud?!
Why, do you miss the dirt, Camia?
Don't worry.
I'll make sure you return
to the grave where you belong.
So? You're confessing
in front of all these people
that you had me buried alive!
I didn't say such a thing.
A typical Ardiente!
You're great at making excuses
right after you slip up!
But not anymore.
You can't salvage
your tarnished reputation.
Because I will see to it
that we will win this election!
[tense music playing]
-Don't be so sure.
-Bring them down!
Bring them down! All of the Ardientes!
-Let's go.
-Bring them down!
Bring them down! All of the Ardientes!
-I swear, that woman, Auntie?
-Emilia, are you okay?
I am going to do something
when I get my position back!
[Emilia grunting]
I can't take it anymore.
I want to smack her in the face!
Shut up, Emilia!
Stop wagging your tongue!
-You know--
-Is it my fault again?!
You know, that had to happen,
so you can wake up to the truth.
You're such an idiot!
Do you know what you did earlier?
You showed the people
that you are unstable,
that you are a psychotic woman!
Why are you blaming it on me again, Papa?!
-I was defending our family!
-You didn't defend anyone!
You only brought more shame to our family!
You women! You truly
are lesser beings than men!
[tense music playing]
Yeah right, Papa!
Well, you men are narrow-minded!
You can't just accept the fact
that our unpredictability
makes you uneasy!
Unpredictability, my ass!
You and your stupid whims!
You're the reason why our plans fail!
It's better if you just shut up
and get out of my face
before I break this on your head!
That's enough! You're going
to hurt somebody again!
I can't let you hurt my wife!
I'll just hurt both of you then!
-Why?
-You always do that!
You always blame me!
And now you want to hit me again, Papa?
-Why?
-That's enough! Let's go!
-Do you like being abused?!
-Why?
Do you enjoy hurting people?!
[Julio] Why? You're starting to like it?!
[Emilia] No!
You're starting to like being slapped!
[tense music playing]
This woman!
Julio.
Congressman.
-Are you okay?
-Guard, guard!
Water, please. Now.
Hon, is he okay?
Just relax? Just relax?
-Water.
-I'm fine!
Call a doctor! Now!
Oh!
If I were Ms. Camia, I would've
shoved Emilia's face in the mud!
So she could experience all
our hardships under their rule!
I'm thankful that they didn't
hurt Aunt Camia.
If they laid a hand on Ms. Camia,
they'd taste the wrath of Team Diego!
That's correct! I'll smack them good!
[laughing]
[pensive music playing]
What is it, Diego?
I need to get out of here.
I'm dragging Aunt Camia into my mess.
This is my fight. I should be facing them!
What are you going to do?
Are you going to accept Jaguar's offer?
Your dad keeps going too far, Emilia!
Everything he's done
to make our lives miserable
will come back to him, mark my words.
You should just accept Jaguar's offer.
[somber music playing]
If you're still hoping
that your dad will help you,
give you a position or power,
that's impossible, Emilia.
Raul, can you just do me a favor?
Can you get me a drink?
I'm going to have a migraine,
a severe one.
That Jaguar guy is just
fooling you, Emilia.
Papa, that's why I need
to meet up with him
so I can turn the tables on him.
Well…
[ominous music playing]
Should you get the chance…
I want you to kill that fool,
so I won't have any more problems.
Okay, Papa.
I'll do exactly what you want me to do.
-Yes!
-But with some conditions.
Conditions?
Yes, Papa.
Now you're giving me conditions?
[tense music playing]
Okay, just for the heck of it.
Come out with it.
-What are your conditions?
-Okay.
First, you'll forget all the mistakes
I've made in the past.
And of course,
you'll also forgive me
for all my faults against you.
And most importantly, you'll allow me
to replace you in congress.
[laughing]
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it. Why not? I'll take it.
But since you're a woman,
I'm sure you're going to fail.
Not this time around, Papa.
I will not fail you
and I promise you that.
[ominous music continues]
[sighs]
-[phone buzzing]
-[suspenseful music playing]
Hello.
Tell them that Jaguar
is ready to meet with them.
How are you, Mom? Are you hurt?
Don't worry about me, Lily. I'm fine.
I can't stop myself from worrying.
If it were up to me,
I would forbid you
from facing off with Emilia.
I'm scared that one day, she'll snap,
grab a gun and…
kill you.
I'm sorry, Lily.
I lost my cool.
I got so infuriated and angry
with that woman.
But I promise it won't happen again.
Mom, I know it's hard.
But as much as possible…
as much as possible, please lie low.
We need to talk about Diego.
I figured that while
the Ardientes are down,
now is the right time to free Diego.
It's time to strengthen his campaign.
Lily, it's going to be difficult.
Because Jaguar's meddling
with Diego's case.
He's another headache.
Okay.
I'll take care of it, Mom.
Your father is right.
You should've just ignored Camia.
Come on, Auntie. Ivy beat me up.
And then that Natalie kidnapped me
and pretended to be Lily Cruz. And now…
I just saw Camia, so I took out
all my anger on her.
It looked like it was
the other way around.
Stop mocking me, Auntie. Come on.
I'll redeem myself.
Don't you worry.
What's your plan?
Well, that's between me and Jaguar.
[tense music playing]
[knocking]
Ma'am, these are for you.
What?
Okay. What's this again?
Hmm…
Gifts.
[chuckles]
Gifts, gifts, gifts. I love gifts.
Stop worrying, Grandpa.
Okay? I will crush Diego's support group.
And I promise you, I'll be epic
in that campaign kickoff.
You better be and you should be.
Because if you fail at your
own event, it'll be your end.
That's not going to happen.
He can't do that and he never will.
Okay?
He can't even leave the prison
I put him in.
I promise you, I will save our position.
I'll take care of our name.
The name Ardiente will continue
to rule the people.
[tense music playing]
Just accept Jaguar's help.
I will accept your offer,
but on one condition.
We have an invitation
from the rival party.
They said we shouldn't miss it.
[Arnaldo] Let me introduce you
all to your future first lady.
-[cheering]
-[applauding]
Ivy Aguas, will you marry me?
-Yes. Yes!
-Yes!
Diego, Diego! Diego, Diego!
Diego, Diego!
-So!
-Diego, Diego!
[Diego] Were you surprised?
Yes, I'm a free man now!
[tense music playing]